<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://wow-life.in/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://wow-life.in/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-12-31T05:04:45+00:00</updated><id>https://wow-life.in/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Wow-L!fe®</title><subtitle>Wow-L!fe website</subtitle><author><name>Nirmal Kumar</name></author><entry><title type="html">Contact Us</title><link href="https://wow-life.in/contact-us" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Contact Us" /><published>2022-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wow-life.in/contact-us</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wow-life.in/contact-us">&lt;p&gt;Treatment is available at Wow-Life clinic off-line and online by prior appointment.
You can organise introductory programs in your place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can enrol your name for the healing treatment and training camps .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;For appointments contact:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;i class=&quot;fa-brands fa-whatsapp&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
 &lt;a href=&quot;tel:+918144444678&quot;&gt; +91 81 44444 678&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa-solid fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:wow_life@dr.com&quot;&gt;wow_life@dr.com | &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:founder@wow-life.in&quot;&gt;founder@wow-life.in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa-brands fa-google-pay fa-2x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;top:-7px;position: relative&quot;&gt;wowlife@axisbank&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us to serve one and all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa-solid fa-location-dot&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;span&gt; New No:133 Old No: 62/1, First floor, Kalathiappan Street, Choolai, Chennai, Tamil Nadu, Pin Code: 600112 India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nirmal Kumar</name></author><summary type="html">Treatment is available at Wow-Life clinic off-line and online by prior appointment. You can organise introductory programs in your place. You can enrol your name for the healing treatment and training camps . For appointments contact: +91 81 44444 678 wow_life@dr.com | founder@wow-life.in wowlife@axisbank Join us to serve one and all. New No:133 Old No: 62/1, First floor, Kalathiappan Street, Choolai, Chennai, Tamil Nadu, Pin Code: 600112 India.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Founder</title><link href="https://wow-life.in/founder" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Founder" /><published>2022-12-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wow-life.in/founder</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wow-life.in/founder">&lt;p&gt;The Anchor of the S!dh healing is Nirmal Chordia, who has been anchoring people since 1996. 
He conducts courses in English, Hindi, Tamil, Rajasthani.
He is in the news in few magazines, Tv shows and he is delivered many invitational / introductions lectures in many establishments and industries since 1996&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our award of thanks to all who are supporting us to spread this wisdom and thousands of people have benefited out of this including many institutions.
(We have conducted programs in many parts of India, Like Chennai, Madurai, Karaikudi, Karaikal, Nagapattinam, Bangalore, Mysore and out of India , like Sri Lanka, USA, Singapore.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;” Wow-L!fe” will continue to contribute articles and invitational / introductory lectures to create awareness about this wisdom of healing.  Your support in this is appreciated for organising Satsang, introductory talks and programs in your area / organisations to keep reaching more and more people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A venue with a maximum of 16 people is the basic requirement of our camps.
It is a non-religious program. No caste, belief or rituals have been adopted. It is open to all.
Many, tailor-made programs for specific groups and for children are also being conducted by us.
We do Distance / Online healing. In special cases, we also do house visits.
We conduct in-house healing programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(We are available but many are not yet open minded to heal themselves.)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nirmal Kumar</name></author><summary type="html">The Anchor of the S!dh healing is Nirmal Chordia, who has been anchoring people since 1996. He conducts courses in English, Hindi, Tamil, Rajasthani. He is in the news in few magazines, Tv shows and he is delivered many invitational / introductions lectures in many establishments and industries since 1996 Our award of thanks to all who are supporting us to spread this wisdom and thousands of people have benefited out of this including many institutions. (We have conducted programs in many parts of India, Like Chennai, Madurai, Karaikudi, Karaikal, Nagapattinam, Bangalore, Mysore and out of India , like Sri Lanka, USA, Singapore.) ” Wow-L!fe” will continue to contribute articles and invitational / introductory lectures to create awareness about this wisdom of healing. Your support in this is appreciated for organising Satsang, introductory talks and programs in your area / organisations to keep reaching more and more people. A venue with a maximum of 16 people is the basic requirement of our camps. It is a non-religious program. No caste, belief or rituals have been adopted. It is open to all. Many, tailor-made programs for specific groups and for children are also being conducted by us. We do Distance / Online healing. In special cases, we also do house visits. We conduct in-house healing programs. (We are available but many are not yet open minded to heal themselves.)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Attain Complete Harmony</title><link href="https://wow-life.in/hormony" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Attain Complete Harmony" /><published>2022-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wow-life.in/hormony</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wow-life.in/hormony">&lt;p&gt;The internal factors of our well being are
the Food, the Breath, the Rest, the Attitude and the Spirit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The external factors of our well being are
the Planets, the Place, the People &amp;amp; the Profession&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need to balance the above two factors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you enrol for the program, we do the complete diagnosis and self evaluation based on the above factors. Then we chart down the training, treatment and counselling needed for every individual, family and organisations, to attain complete well being and harmony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Treatment and Training forms the two arms of the activities of Wow-L!fe, while the former is curative, the latter is preventive. Healing the body and the mind of the current state of dis-ease, one is equipped with the wisdom to prevent such imbalances in future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A thirst for wisdom is the only criteria for enrolling in the Healing Awareness program “S!dh” which takes care of following&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Body Awareness&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;inline-list&quot;&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;HEALTHY FOOD HABIT&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;REJUVENATING EXERCISES&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;FITNESS YOGA ASANAS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Breath Awareness&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;inline-list&quot;&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;BASIC MUDHRA PRANAYAMA&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;ADVANCE SIDDH PRANAYAMA&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;COOLING PRANAYAMA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Mind Awareness&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;inline-list&quot;&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;CONSCIOUS MIND&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;SUBCONSCIOUS MIND&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;SUPER CONSCIOUS MIND&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Self Awareness&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;inline-list&quot;&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;KNOW THYSELF&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;LOVE THY SELF&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;ALL THY SELF&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Time &amp;amp; Space Awareness&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;inline-list&quot;&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;ASTROLOGY&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;VASTHU&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;SAMADHI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Nirmal Kumar</name></author><summary type="html">The internal factors of our well being are the Food, the Breath, the Rest, the Attitude and the Spirit. The external factors of our well being are the Planets, the Place, the People &amp;amp; the Profession We need to balance the above two factors. When you enrol for the program, we do the complete diagnosis and self evaluation based on the above factors. Then we chart down the training, treatment and counselling needed for every individual, family and organisations, to attain complete well being and harmony. Treatment and Training forms the two arms of the activities of Wow-L!fe, while the former is curative, the latter is preventive. Healing the body and the mind of the current state of dis-ease, one is equipped with the wisdom to prevent such imbalances in future. A thirst for wisdom is the only criteria for enrolling in the Healing Awareness program “S!dh” which takes care of following Body Awareness HEALTHY FOOD HABIT REJUVENATING EXERCISES FITNESS YOGA ASANAS Breath Awareness BASIC MUDHRA PRANAYAMA ADVANCE SIDDH PRANAYAMA COOLING PRANAYAMA Mind Awareness CONSCIOUS MIND SUBCONSCIOUS MIND SUPER CONSCIOUS MIND Self Awareness KNOW THYSELF LOVE THY SELF ALL THY SELF Time &amp;amp; Space Awareness ASTROLOGY VASTHU SAMADHI</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">S!DH HEAL!NG</title><link href="https://wow-life.in/sidh-healing" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="S!DH HEAL!NG" /><published>2022-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wow-life.in/sidh-healing</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wow-life.in/sidh-healing">&lt;p&gt;Universal self- that is the meaning of the Prakrit language “SIDH”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being Sidh brings awareness about an energy to the needy and thus healing happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each of us has at some time or other in our lives in the time of need, we made available for the needy by way of  touch, taste, smell, sight and sound, which healed them.
It creates harmony in “Panch Boothas”, the five Great energies Earth, Water, Fire, Air and Ether of which the universe is made up off, thus heals self and others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This simple act backed by the selfless intention to be available to support healing is the strong foundation for all forms of energy work, the system of medicines and therapies.
It is not magic but it is not less than magic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that is needed is an anchor, by way of few, simple guidelines for the happenings of healing to take place. It is for the body, the mind, the time, the space and beyond.
It is for all because we, at Wow-L!fe, Just “BE” and Healing Happens !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neither I AM  THIS nor I AM THAT. ! AM ALL ! - Ramana Papaji&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nirmal Kumar</name></author><summary type="html">Universal self- that is the meaning of the Prakrit language “SIDH”. Being Sidh brings awareness about an energy to the needy and thus healing happens. Each of us has at some time or other in our lives in the time of need, we made available for the needy by way of touch, taste, smell, sight and sound, which healed them. It creates harmony in “Panch Boothas”, the five Great energies Earth, Water, Fire, Air and Ether of which the universe is made up off, thus heals self and others. This simple act backed by the selfless intention to be available to support healing is the strong foundation for all forms of energy work, the system of medicines and therapies. It is not magic but it is not less than magic. All that is needed is an anchor, by way of few, simple guidelines for the happenings of healing to take place. It is for the body, the mind, the time, the space and beyond. It is for all because we, at Wow-L!fe, Just “BE” and Healing Happens ! Neither I AM THIS nor I AM THAT. ! AM ALL ! - Ramana Papaji</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wow-L!fe</title><link href="https://wow-life.in/home" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wow-L!fe" /><published>2022-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wow-life.in/home</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wow-life.in/home">&lt;div class=&quot;logo&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;h4 class=&quot;logo-sub-text&quot;&gt;S&lt;span class=&quot;logo-text-highlight&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;dh Heal&lt;span class=&quot;logo-text-highlight&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;ng&lt;/h4&gt;
    &lt;h6&gt;Since 1996&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;As light eliminates darkness, thus &quot;S!dh eliminates disease&quot; - Nirmal&lt;/h5&gt;</content><author><name>Nirmal Kumar</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>